justraveling.com 2018-09-01

# Privacy Policy - Justraveling

Your privacy is important to us, and it’s our policy to respect it regarding any information we may collect while operating our website. Accordingly, we have developed this policy in order for you to understand how we collect, use, communicate and disclose and make use of personal information.  
The following outlines our Privacy Policy:

  * Before or at the time of collecting personal information, we will identify the purposes for which information is being collected.
  * We will collect and use of personal information solely with the objective of fulfilling those purposes specified by us and for other compatible purposes, unless we obtain the consent of the individual concerned or as required by law.
  * We will only retain personal information as long as necessary for the fulfillment of those purposes.
  * We will collect personal information by lawful and fair means and, where appropriate, with the knowledge or consent of the individual concerned.
  * Personal data should be relevant to the purposes for which it is to be used, and, to the extent necessary for those purposes, should be accurate, complete, and up-to-date.
  * We neither rent nor sell your personal information to anyone.
  * We will protect personal information by reasonable security safeguards against loss or theft, as well as unauthorized access, disclosure, copying, use or modification.
  * We will make readily available to customers information about our policies and practices relating to the management of personal information.

In addition, a number of our pages use first and third-party’s cookies to:

  1. recognise your computer when you visit our website
  2. improve the website’s usability
  3. analyse the use of our website
  4. personalise our website for you

Enabling these cookies is not strictly necessary for the website to work but it will provide you with a better browsing experience. You can delete or block these cookies, but if you do that some features of this site may not work as intended. The cookie-related information is not used to identify you personally and the pattern data is fully under our control. These cookies are not used for any purpose other than those described here.

We are committed to ensure that the confidentiality of personal information is protected and maintained. Justraveling.com may amend its Privacy Policy from time to time. Use of information we collect now is subject to the Privacy Policy in effect at the time such information is used. If we make changes in the way we use personal information, we will notify you by posting an announcement on our website or sending you an email.

If you have any questions regarding this Privacy Policy, please send us an email.

**Last Revised: May, 2016**

This website uses cookies to improve your experience. We'll assume you're fine with this, but you can opt-out if you wish. OK -or- Learn More
